{
    "id": "8b49d8bdb8c843fcad70e680283110e4",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This table is made ……………………….. teak wood.",
            "description": "We say make of when we identify the material used to make something.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aadad4daf18c4640be4ebb15b82154ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going …………………….",
            "description": "No preposition is used before home when we are referring to direction.",
            "answers": [
                "to home",
                "for home",
                "home"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "43ab91beb2a44153b4218247b3919fe3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He hit me ……………………….. a stick.",
            "description": "We use ‘with’ to talk about the tool and 'by' to talk about the agent.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d4cfd7ac6df7474b97e195351682e98f"
        },
        {
            "question": "India has been independent …………………………",
            "description": "With perfect tenses we use since, not from.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "from",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "962492295aa5490aaacbaec1811cef8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wrote ………………………….",
            "description": "Before a personal object, we use ‘write to’.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "to me",
                "at me"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bec9138e004649ffbb7d3c144d45c678"
        },
        {
            "question": "Divide this money ……………………………. the brothers.",
            "description": "We can use divide among or divide between before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "among",
                "between",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "45431d3126f84495982ea2be7e82f465"
        },
        {
            "question": "He invited me ………………………. dinner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "60e9389f7ce048c6af776a5321839119"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………….. Delhi in the morning.",
            "description": "We do not use a preposition after reach.",
            "answers": [
                "reached",
                "reached at",
                "reached in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "17f1c7ae6620410e9cc065a1d1c4231e"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is a common practice ………………………. the Hindus.",
            "description": "Between is used with two or more clearly separate people or things. Among is used for a crowd or a mass of people. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "between",
                "among"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "67602a71fa20475ab784961c6bec6cf5"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is a good house to ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "live in",
                "live at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "34fc7ad4ab4a4d3d9c4044d8b1aad72c"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the road to ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "go on",
                "go by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "92db6e74b5614ff29b38486890c30f78"
        },
        {
            "question": "I gave him a chair to ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sit",
                "sit at",
                "sit on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "625ea42c58be4054979e50a812b04276"
        }
    ]
}